A Guide to the University of Virginia Student Council Appropriations Committee General Records 1946-1975
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Student Council Appropriations Committee General Records 1946-1975
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/2/6.791
This collection consists of 5,400 items, which are ca. 4.5 linear feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection is an archival transfer from the Reference Department, Alderman Library University of Virginia on 1979 September 7.
Scope and Content Information
General records of the Appropriations Committee, a standing committee of Student Council and the committee responsible for reviewing requests from student organizations for recognition as University sanctioned organizations. The records consist primarily of files on the individual organizations applying for funding including sports and hobby clubs, various sororities and fraternities, student publications, musical organizations, and student branches of professional associations and political parties.
Of interest are the files from goups representing the influx of African American students in the 1970s, and groups originating in the student protest movements of the 1960s and 1970s such as draft resistance organizations, Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), and the Youth International Party (YIPPIE).
The collection also contains records of the Student Activities Committee, 1956-1971, a faculty commitee charged by the Board of Visitors to administer the distribution of student activity fee funds prior to the assumption of this duty by the Student Council.
Contents List
- Series I: Committee Files
  - General Allocations 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Organizations and Publications 1967 Fall (Box 1)
  - Organizations and Publications 1968 Fall (Box 1)
  - Organizations and Publications Study - G.R.C. 1968 (Box 1)
  - Publications Committee 1946-1950 (Box 1)
  - Regulations and Instructions for the Requesting of Funds by Student Organizations 1966 May (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee Minutes 1956 Spring (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1956 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1957 Spring (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1957 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1958 Spring (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1858-1959 (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1959 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1960 (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1960 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1962 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1963 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1964 Spring (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1965 Spring (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1965 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1966 Spring (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1966 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1967 Spring (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1967 Fall (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1968 Spring (Box 1)
  - Student Activities Committee 1968 Fall (Box 2)
  - Student Activities Committee 1969 Spring (Box 2)
  - Student Activities Committee History 1956 - 1965, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Student Council Recommendations to Student Activities Committee 1970-1971 (Box 2)
- Series II: Files on Organizations
  - Action Ministries 1971-1975 (Box 2)
  - Ad Hoc Caroling Committee 1973-1975 (Box 2)
  - AKIBA 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Alderman Judicial Council n.d. (Box 2)
  - Alderman Legislative Council 1969-1972 (Box 2)
  - Alderman Road Social Organization n.d. (Box 2)
  - Alpha Epsilon Delta 1973-1975 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Kappa Pi Social Club 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Kappa Psi 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Kappa Psi 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Omega Alpha 1960 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Phi Omega 1969-1976 (Box 2)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Student Chapter 1971-1975 (Box 2)
  - American Friends of Free Palestine 1970-1974 (Box 2)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - American Institute of Architects 1941, 1955, 1967-1969 (Box 2)
  - American Institute of Chemical Engineers 1966-1970 (Box 2)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers 1970-1975 (Box 2)
  - Anchorage, The 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Angel Flight 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Anglers Society 1965 (Box 2)
  - Anthropology Association 1971-1975 (Box 2)
  - Architectural Council 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Arnold Air Society 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Artist Series 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Asian Studies Club 1969-1975 (Box 2)
  - Association of Education Students 1973-1975 (Box 2)
  - Association of Residential Councils 1971-1975 (Box 2)
  - Association of Students for Israel 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Ayn Rand Society 1967 (Box 3)
  - Bacchus Society 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Backgammon Club 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Bad Check Committee 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Black Americans Law Student Association 1970-1975 (Box 3)
  - Bangladesh Information Committee 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - The Barrister 1967-1976 (Box 3)
  - Basketball Club, UVA 1971-1974 (Box 3)
  - Beaux Arts Ball Committee 1972-1974 (Box 3)
  - Black Student Alliance 1968-1975 (Box 3)
  - Black Students for Freedom 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Blue Ridge Mountain Buddhist Meditation Group 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Blue Ridge Mountain Rescue Group 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Boolean Society 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Bowling Club 1968-1976 (Box 3)
  - Bridge Club 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - Business Forum 1967-1976 (Box 3)
  - "CARE" (Campus Association for Research & Enlightenment 1972-1974 (Box 3)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ 1972-1974 (Box 3)
  - Catalyst for Renewed Community 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - The Cavalier Daily 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Cave Club 1967-1975 (Box 3)
  - Celebration Fellowship 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Centro Hispanico 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville- Albemarle Citizens for McGovern 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville- Albemarle Citizens vs. the ABM n.d. (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville Draft Counseling Group 1967-1973 (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville Draft Opposition 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville Draft Resistance 1969-1973 (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville Friends of the Earth 1972-1974 (Box 3)
  - Cheerleaders 1964-1968 (Box 3)
  - Chinese Students Association 1971-1974 (Box 3)
  - Christian Medical Fellowships n.d. (Box 3)
  - Christian Science Organization, UVA 1972-1974 (Box 3)
  - Christian Together 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints Student Association 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Classics Club 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Colonnade Club n.d. (Box 3)
  - Committee for Responsible Allocations 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Committee for Responsible Leadership n.d. (Box 4)
  - Committee to Send Letter to Congress 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Community Dance Committee 1971-1975 (Box 4)
  - Computer User's Group 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Congressional Action Fund 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Counsellor's Committee on Human Sexuality 1972-1975 (Box 4)
  - Creative Anachronism, Society for 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Crescent Club 1972-1974 (Box 4)
  - The Declaration 1973-1975 (Box 4)
  - December Coalition 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - Delta Sigma Pi 1965 (Box 4)
  - Delta Sigma Rho - Tau Kappa Alpha n.d. (Box 4)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority 1972-1974 (Box 4)
  - Delta Theta Phi 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Design Council 1969-1972 (Box 4)
  - Discordian Society 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Dobie Dorm - Class of '75 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Draft Counseling Group 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Duplicate Bridge Club 1973-1975 (Box 4)
  - Eastern Shore Club n.d. (Box 4)
  - Echols Math Club 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Economics Club 1967-1975 (Box 4)
  - Education Review Association 1963-1967 (Box 4)
  - El Centro Hispanico 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Engineer's Club 1971-1974 (Box 4)
  - Engineering Council 1966-1975 (Box 4)
  - English Club 1971-1976 (Box 4)
  - Environmental Sciences Club 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Essays in History 1972-1975 (Box 4)
  - Eta Kappa Nu (Gamma Pi Chapter) 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Executive Board of Graduating Class 1974 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Experimental University 1968-1976 (Box 4)
  - Extra-Legal Forum 1971-1974 (Box 4)
  - Family Practice Club 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - Fast 1974 (Box 4)
  - Federation of Americans Supporting Science & Technology (FASST) 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Fencing Club 1969-1975 (Box 5)
  - Festival of Life-Peace Foundation, Inc. 1969-1970 (Box 5)
  - Field Artillery and Saluting Battery 1970-1973 (Box 5)
  - Field Hockey Club 1971-1974 (Box 5)
  - Film Production Union 1973-1975 (Box 5)
  - Filmwatchers Club n.d. (Box 5)
  - Finance Club 1974-1976 (Box 5)
  - First Year Directory 1968 (Box 5)
  - First Yearmen for Better Government 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - 507 Dude Ranch Five-O-Seven 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Focus 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - Folk Dance Club 1972-1975 (Box 5)
  - Folk Music Club n.d. (Box 5)
  - Foundations I 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - French Club (Le Cercle Francais) 1972-1974 (Box 5)
  - Friends of the Quang Ngai Hospital 1971-1972 (Box 5)
  - Friends of Spiro 1969 (Box 5)
  - Fuck Obscenity League 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - Garrett A. Hobart Historical Society 1971-1974 (Box 5)
  - German Club 1969-1975 (Box 5)
  - Glee Club 1967-1974 (Box 5)
  - Go Society n.d. (Box 5)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs Association 1965-1969 (Box 5)
  - Graduate Education Association 1965-1977 (Box 5)
  - Graduate Residence Council 1971-1972 (Box 5)
  - Graduate Student Council 1972-1974 (Box 5)
  - Graduate Student Government 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Graduate Student Government - Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 5)
  - Graduate Wives in Arts and Sciences 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Guerilla Theater Coalition 1972 (Box 5)
  - Gymnastics Club 1967-1974 (Box 5)
  - Hackensack 1968 (Box 5)
  - Handball Club n.d. (Box 5)
  - Hans Linnartz Emulation Society 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - High School Recruiting Committee n.d. (Box 5)
  - Historical Simulation Society 1972-1975 (Box 5)
  - History Club 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Howell for Governor Committee 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Ice Hockey Club 1973-1975 (Box 5)
  - India Association of Charlottesville 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Institute of Electrical & Electronic Engineers 1970-1975 (Box 6)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute 1973-1975 (Box 6)
  - Intercom 1974-1976 (Box 6)
  - Interfaith Action Committee 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - International Club 1967-1975 (Box 6)
  - International Relations Organization 1973-1975 (Box 6)
  - Italian Club 1972-1976 (Box 6)
  - Jazz Ensemble 1971-1975 (Box 6)
  - 1705 Jefferson Park Authority 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Jefferson Party 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Jefferson Sabres Society 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Jefferson Society 1959-1975 (Box 6)
  - Jeffersonian 1965-1968 (Box 6)
  - Karate & Self-Defense Club 1969-1975 (Box 6)
  - Lacrosse, Women's Undergraduate Club 1973-1975 (Box 6)
  - Larry Joseph Sabato Memorial Bombastic Society, The 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - Law Partners 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Law School Admissions Committee 1970-1975 (Box 6)
  - Law School Young Republican Club 1967 (Box 6)
  - Law Students Civil Rights Research Council 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - Law Students Civil Rights Research Council 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - Lawn Chowder and Marching Society 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Le Cercle Francais 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Legal Assistance Society 1968-1975 (Box 6)
  - Legal Environment Group 1968-1975 (Box 6)
  - Legal Research Group 1963 (Box 6)
  - Liquifactionist Party and Birth Control Club 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - LOKI- UVA Science Magazine 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Lychnos Society 1954-1969 (Box 6)
  - The James Madison Society 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Madison House 1970-1975 (Box 6)
  - Mark Robinson Memorial Ran Club and Lonely Hearts Pep Band Society, The 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - Marketing Club 1974-1976 (Box 6)
  - Maury Associates 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Medical Circle 1971-1975 (Box 7)
  - Medical Community 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - Medical History Society of the University of Virginia 1973-1974 (Box 7)
  - J. B. Minor Pre-Legal Society 1968-1975 (Box 7)
  - Modern Dance Club 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - Monroe Rifles, Army ROTC 1971-1973 (Box 7)
  - J. B. Moore Society of International Law 1967-1975 (Box 7)
  - Most Ignoble, Dishonorable, and Detestable Society for the Propagation of Decadence and Debauchery of the UVA 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - Moto-Cross Club, UVA 1972-1974 (Box 7)
  - Mulholland Society 1968-1975 (Box 7)
  - Mary Munford-Roberta Gwathmey Area Council 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - Muslim Student Association 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - Newman Student Association 1960; 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Northern Virginia Student Vote, UVA 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - NROTC Honor Guard 1972-1975 (Box 7)
  - Nursing School Student Council 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - Omega Fuss Coalition 1973-1974 (Box 7)
  - Omega Psi Phi Fraternity 1973-1975 (Box 7)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1957; 1966-1969 (Box 7)
  - Opportunity Consultants, Inc. 1970-1975 (Box 7)
  - Organization of Professional Anarchist & Effete Impudent Snobs 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Organizations and Publications Reports 1957-1966 (Box 7)
  - Outing Club 1964-1975 (Box 7)
  - Patrick Henry Society 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Pep Band 1970-1975 (Box 7)
  - Phi Alpha Delta Law Fraternity 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Phi Alpha Theta 1973-1976 (Box 7)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1971 (Box 7)
  - Phi Beta Sigma Fraternity (Cresent Club) 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Phi Delta Phi Legal Fraternity n.d. (Box 8)
  - Phi Eta Sigma n.d. (Box 8)
  - Phi Eta Sigma 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Phi Sigma Society (Beta Delta Chapter) 1967-1971 (Box 8)
  - Philosophy Club 197201976 (Box 8)
  - Physics Society 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Pi Lamda Colony 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Piedmont Rural Research Corporation 1971-1975 (Box 8)
  - PK-German Society n.d. (Box 8)
  - Planned Parenthood of Central Virginia 1971-1974 (Box 8)
  - Planning Students Association 1971-1972 (Box 8)
  - Plume and Sword 1962-1967 (Box 8)
  - Polo Club 1967-1975 (Box 8)
  - Population Fund Committee 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Post Conviction Assistance Project 1971-1975 (Box 8)
  - P. P. Barbour Memorial Award Committee 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Primi Lumi Society 1971-1975 (Box 8)
  - Prism Coffee House 1970-1975 (Box 8)
  - Progressive Engineering Party 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - The Puppy Party 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - Quebec - Labrador Volunteers of Virginia 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Radical Student Union 1969-1972 (Box 8)
  - Radicals for Capitalism 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Railway Historical Society 1970-1972 (Box 8)
  - John Randolph Society 1965 (Box 8)
  - Rapier 1967-1969 (Box 8)
  - Raven Society 1953; 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - The Record 1971-1973 (Box 8)
  - Registered Nurses Student Association 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Restoration Ball Committee 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Rho Epsilon Delta 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Riding Club 1971-1975 (Box 8)
  - Rifle and Pistol Club 1968-1975 (Box 8)
  - Rowing Association, Women's 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Rugby 1968-1975 (Box 8)
  - Sailing Association 1970-1975 (Box 8)
  - St. Thomas Hall 1970-1974 (Box 8)
  - Scarab Honor Fraternity 1967-1979 (Box 8)
  - Sceptre Society n.d. (Box 8)
  - Semper Fidelis Society n.d. (Box 8)
  - Sigma Alpha Club n.d. (Box 8)
  - Sigma Alpha Eta n.d. (Box 8)
  - Sigma Delta Pi 1965 (Box 8)
  - Sigma Gamma Epsilon 1965 (Box 8)
  - Sigma Pi Sigma 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Ski Club 1971-1975 (Box 8)
  - Skull and Keys n.d. (Box 8)
  - Social Movements Collection 1970-1976 (Box 9)
  - Society for Interdisciplinary Study 1971-1972 (Box 9)
  - Society of American Military Engineers 1973-1974 (Box 9)
  - Society of Automotive Engineers 1971-1972 (Box 9)
  - Society of Individualists n.d. (Box 9)
  - Society of Physics Students 1968-1975 (Box 9)
  - Society of the Cornish Game Hen 1969-1971 (Box 9)
  - The Society of the Golden Gonads 1969-1970 (Box 9)
  - Sociology-Anthropology Club 1969-1970 (Box 9)
  - Sociology Association 1973-1975 (Box 9)
  - Southeastern Review 1972-1975 (Box 9)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Spirit Club n.d. (Box 9)
  - SPLIBS 1969-1970 (Box 9)
  - Standard White Memorial Society 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Club 1973-1974 (Box 9)
  - Student Art Association 1973-1975 (Box 9)
  - Student Athletic Council 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Student Dating Service 1969-1971 (Box 9)
  - Student Legal Defense Fund Committee n.d. (Box 9)
  - Student Legal Forum 1966-1975 (Box 9)
  - Student Musicians of UVA 1973-1974 (Box 9)
  - Student Nurses Association 1971-1975 (Box 9)
  - Students for Byrd 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Students for Social Action 1964-1966 (Box 9)
  - Students for a Democratic Society 1967-1971 (Box 9)
  - Students in Support of the Transition Program: 1969 1969 (Box 9)
  - Students United for a New University Publication 1969-1970 (Box 9)
  - Symphonic Band 1959-1975 (Box 9)
  - Synchronized Swimming 1972-1975 (Box 9)
  - Table Tennis 1972-1975 (Box 9)
  - Tau Beta Pi 1971-1974 (Box 9)
  - Tennis Club 1969-1974 (Box 9)
  - Theta Tau n.d. (Box 9)
  - The Three Society (Secret Society) 1969 (Box 9)
  - Transition, UVA n.d. (Box 9)
  - Trident Society 1972-1973; n.d. (Box 9)
  - Tuesday Evening Concert Series 1966-1969 (Box 9)
  - Uncle Moses Brigade n.d. (Box 9)
  - Unicorn 1969-1972 (Box 9)
  - Union Democracy Project 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - Union of University Students 1970-1974 (Box 10)
  - United Students for Action 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - University Cultural Forum 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - University Cycle Club 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - University Forum 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - University Guide Service 1968-1974 (Box 10)
  - University Lobby 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - University of Virginia Amateur Radio Club 1971-1975 (Box 10)
  - University of Virginia College Life 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - University of Virginia Democrats 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - University of Virginia Magazine 1956-1969 (Box 10)
  - University of Virginia Undergrad Young Americans for Freedom 1971-1973 (Box 10)
  - University Party 1968-1970 (Box 10)
  - University Philately Society 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - University Restaurant Committee 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - University Singers 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - University Students for Crater 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - University Volunteer Services Bureau 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Christian Fellowship 1965-1971 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Collegium Antiquum 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Council on Human Relations - Martin Luther King, Jr. Chapter 1970 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Debaters 1969-1975 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Field Staff of National Committee on United States-China Relations, Inc. 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Graduate Law Students 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Guerilla Players 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Journal of International Law 1970-1975 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Law Weekly 1968-1975 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Law Women 1971-1975 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Off-Road Riders 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Players 1965-1975 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Progressive Party 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Radio Theatre Ensemble 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Research Institute 1969-1973 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Students for Community Health 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Veterans for Peace 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Temperance Union (VIRTU) 1073-1974 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Weekly 1969-1974 (Box 11)
  - Virginia Welfare Rights Organization 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Virginia Youth Coalition for Muskie 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Volunteer Services Bureau 1969 (Box 11)
  - Wargame Club, UVA n.d. (Box 11)
  - The Way 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Whispering Glades Polo Club 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Windlass 1971-1975 (Box 11)
  - W.I.T.C.H. n.d. (Box 11)
  - Women's Chorus 1973-1976 (Box 11)
  - WTJU Radio 1965-1975 (Box 11)
  - WUVA Radio 1947-1975 (Box 11)
  - YMCA 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - Young Democrats 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - Young Republicans 1968-1975 (Box 11)
  - Youth International Party Conspiracy (YIPPIE) n.d. (Box 11)
  - Zero Population Growth 1970-1973 (Box 11)
  - Zeta Omicron Omicron 1971-1973 (Box 11)